Guide to the Charles W. Duncan, Jr. business papers, 1958-2013 MS 583
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III. Deputy Secretary of Defense and Secretary of Energy appointments, 1977-1981, 160577
  - Sub-Series I. Bound Volumes, 1979-1981, n.d.; 143778
    - Office of Management and Budget, Correspondence signed by Secretary of Energy, August 1979-January 1981; 143794 (Box 17)
    - Remarks, Speeches, Testimony and Talking Points of Honorable Charles W. Duncan, Jr., Secretary of Energy. Volume I, July-December 1979.; 143795 (Box 17)
    - Remarks, Speeches, Testimony and Talking Points of Honorable Charles W. Duncan, Jr., Secretary of Energy. Volume II, January-March 1980; 143796 (Box 17)
    - Remarks, Speeches, Testimony and Talking Points of Honorable Charles W. Duncan, Jr., Secretary of Energy. Volume III, April-June 1980; 143797 (Box 17)
    - Remarks, Speeches, Testimony and Talking Points of Honorable Charles W. Duncan, Jr., Secretary of Energy. Volume IV, July-January 1981; 143798 (Box 17)
    - Minutes, Senior Staff Meetings. Department of Energy. Volume I, August-December 1979; 143799 (Box 17)
    - Minutes, Senior Staff Meetings. Department of Energy. Volume II, January 1980-January 1981; 143800 (Box 17)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume I, August-October 1979; 143801 (Box 18)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume II, November-December 1979; 143802 (Box 18)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume III, January-February 1980; 143803 (Box 18)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume IV, March-April 1980; 143804 (Box 18)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume V, May-June 1980; 143805 (Box 18)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume VI, July-August 1980; 143806 (Box 18)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume VII, September-October 1980; 143807 (Box 19)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume VIII, November-December 1980; 143808 (Box 19)
    - Department of Energy Weekly Activity Reports, Volume IX, January 1981; 143809 (Box 19)
    - Interagency Correspondence signed by Secretary of Energy and Deputy Secretary of Energy, Volume I, Executive Departments, 143810 (Box 19)
    - Interagency Correspondence signed by Secretary of Energy and Deputy Secretary of Energy, Volume II, A-N, 143811 (Box 19)
    - Interagency Correspondence signed by Secretary of Energy and Deputy Secretary of Energy, Volume III, O-Z, 143812 (Box 19)
    - White House Correspondence, Volume I, August-December 1979; 143989 (Box 20)
    - White House Correspondence, Volume II, January-March 1980; 143990 (Box 20)
    - White House Correspondence, Volume III, April 1980-January 1981; 143991 (Box 20)
    - Congressional Testimony Secretary of Energy Volume I, July 1979-April 1980; 143992 (Box 20)
    - Congressional Testimony Secretary of Energy Volume II, May-July 1980; 143993 (Box 20)
    - Appointment books, 1977-1981; 161955 (Box 21)
  - Sub-Series II. Scrapbooks & Trip Books, 1977-1980; 143779
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, January-May 1977; 143813 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, June 1977; 143814 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, July 1977; 143815 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, July-August 1977; 143816 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, September-October 1977; 143817 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, November 1977; 143818 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, November-December 1977; 143819 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, January 1978; 143820 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, February 1978; 143821 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, March 1978; 143822 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, March 1978; 143823 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, March 1978; 143824 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, North Korean Coverage of 12 March Joint Exercise Activity, 1978; 143825 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, April-June 1978; 143826 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, July 1978; 143827 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, August 1978; 143828 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, September 1978; 143829 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, September 1978; 143830 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, October 1978; 143831 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, November-December 1978; 143832 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, January-February 1979; 143833 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, March 1979; 143834 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, April-July 1979; 143835 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Scrapbook, July-August 1979; 143836 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, Leaving Ceremony Department of Defense, August 1979; 143837 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, Swearing-In Ceremony, August 1979; 143838 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, Photographs, August-September 1979; 143839 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, Photographs, August-September 1979; 143840 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, September 1979; 143841 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, October 1979; 143842 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, November 1979; 143843 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, December 1979; 143844 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, January-February 1980; 143845 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, Photographs, February-March 1980; 143846 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, April-May 1980; 143847 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, May-June 1980; 143848 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, Declaration of the Venice Summit, June 22-23, 1980; 143849 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, July-August 1980; 143850 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, September-October 1980; 143851 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, November 1980; 143852 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Secretary of Energy Scrapbook, December 1980-January 1981; 143853 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - President Carter's Visit to Panama, (3 folders), June 16-17, 1978; 143855 (Box 22, Folder 42-44)
    - Department of Defense Egypt Visit, October 1978; 143856 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Visit to Iran, October 23-26, 1978; 143857 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Department of Defense Saudi Arabia Itinerary, October 26-27, 1978; 143858 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense Visit to Kenya, October 29, 1978; 143859 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Sudan, October 31-November 1, 1978; 143860 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, November 1-4, 1978; 143889 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Secretary of Energy trip Saudi Arabia, March 1-4, 1980; 143861 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - President Carter Visit to Rome, the Vatican, Venice, Belgrade, Madrid & Lisbon, June 20-25, 1980; 143862 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series III. Subject Files, 1977-1981.; 143781
    - Deputy Secretary of Defense, 1977-79; 161957
      - Brochures: Pearl Harbor and Hawaii, [March 1978]; 143932 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Cabinet Meeting Notes, 1977-79; 161956 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Camp David Retreat Guest List, April 16-17, 1978; 143885 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Chronological File, January-June 1977; 161958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence [Incoming] - Direct, January-December 1977; 161961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence [Incoming], January 4-February 17, 1977; 161959 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence [Incoming], February 18-June 21, 1977; 161960 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence [Incoming], June-September 1977; 161962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence [Incoming] - Direct, January-June 1978; 161963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence [Incoming] - Direct, June-December 1978; 161964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence [Incoming], March-December 1978; 161965 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence [Incoming] - Direct, January-June 1979; 161966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence [Incoming], January-June 1979; 161968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence [Chronological], July-December 1979, July 1980; 161969 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence-Letters of Resignation, 1977; 161970 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, A-G, 1977; 161971 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, H-O, 1977; 161972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, P-Z, 1977; 161973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Daily Log, December 27, 1976-April 8, 1977; 161974 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Daily Log, April 9, 1977-August 29, 1977; 161975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Daily Log, August 30, 1977-December 31, 1977; 161976 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Daily Log, January 3, 1978-April 24, 1978; 161977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Daily Log, April 25, 1978-August 10, 1978; 161978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Daily Log, August 11, 1978-December 30, 1978; 161979 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Disclosure - Working file (3 folders), 161982 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
      - Financial Disclosures, 1977-79; 161980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Hearings (Nomination)/Confirmation files (2 folders), 1977; 161981 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
      - Inaugural Guide to Washington., January 1977; 143872 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - [Mr. & Mrs. Duncan] Inaugural Schedule, January 1977; 143873 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - [President Carter] Inauguration invitation, tickets and program, January 1977; 143879 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Menus, 1978; 143931 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Meeting on Ethics Act, 1979; 161983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1976-1978; 143863 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Personal Biographical File (3 folders), 161984 (Box 24, Folder 13-15)
      - Photographs: Racquetball at Pentagon Officer's Athletic Club, [1978]; 143868 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Plaque: NORAD Headquarters, August 12, 1977; 162029 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Printed Materials: Government Executive, April 1978; 143930 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Printed Materials: US Congressional Record with note from J.J. Pickle., July 13, 1977; 143880 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Program: Panama Canal Treaties, [1977]; 143929 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Remarks of James B. Stockdale., February 18, 1977; 143896 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Travel Vouchers, 1977-79; 161985 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Year 1977 (3 folders), 161986 (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
    - Secretary of Energy, 1979-1981; 161987
      - Background Readings - Bare Bones, Book III, 161988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Background Readings - Issues, Book II, 161989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Briefing Memorandum, 161990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Cabinet Meeting Notes, 161991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Certificate of Appreciation, National Press Club, June 26, 1980; 143899 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Chronological Files, January 1980-January 1981; 161992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence - Incoming [Direct], July 1979-October 1980; 161993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence - [Incoming], November 1979-January 1981; 161994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, A, 161995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, B, 161996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, C, 161997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, D, 161998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, E, 161999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, F, 162000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, G, 162001 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, H, 162002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, I, 162003 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, J, 162004 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, K, 162005 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, L, 162006 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, Mc, 162007 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, M, 162008 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, N, 162009 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, O, 162010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, P, 162011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, R, 162012 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, S, 162013 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, T, 162014 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, U-V, 162015 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, W, 162016 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence-Congratulatory letters, XYZ, 162017 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence-Farewell letters/Washington, 1981; 162018 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence-Farewell letters, At-a-boy letters, 1981; 162019 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Declassified weekly reports: from International Affairs and Defense Programs, 1981; 162020 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Economic issues, 162021 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Files to Historian, 1981; 162022 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - [Department of Defense/Department of Energy] Filing, 162023 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Financial Disclosure Report, 1980; 162024 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - The First 100 days - Book I, 162025 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Hearings (Nomination)/Confirmation files (4 folders), 162026 (Box 26, Folder 18-21)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1979; 143864 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1980-1983; 143865 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Personnel papers, 162027 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Photographs: [Secretary of Energy] Nomination Hearing, 1979; 143867 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Photographs: Oak Ridge, Tennessee visit, 1979-1980; 143870 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Photographs: White House, 1978-1981; 143869 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Political travel, 162028 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Presidential Memos, 162030 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - President's Program for US Energy Security (2 folders), 162031 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
      - President's Program for US Energy Security-Briefing book, 162032 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Printed Materials: Energy Consumer, January 1980; 143895 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Printed Materials: Energy Insider, September 3, 1979; 143894 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Printed Materials: Executive Bio-pictorial directory, 1980; 143881 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Printed Materials: National Journal, July 28, 1979; 143891 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Printed Materials: Newsweek, July 30, 1979; 143892 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Printed Materials: Time, July 30, 1979; 143933 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Printed Materials: U.S. News & World Report, July 30, 1979; 143934 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Printed Materials: U.S. News & World Report published interview, photographs, correspondence, February 1980; 143866 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Printed Materials: The White House News & Views, August 28, 1979; 143893 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Programs, 1979; 143876 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Programs, 1980; 143877 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Program: Presidential Medal of Freedom, January 1981; 143878 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Remarks of the President in his address to the Nation. Signed by President Jimmy Carter, July 30, 1979; 143886 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Remarks Swearing-In for Energy Secretary Charles W. Duncan, Jr, August 24, 1979; 143884 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Re-election campaign Carter/Mondale (2 folders), 1980; 143887 (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
      - Report: Jimmy Carter "Brief Report", May 1981; 143888 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Resignation, 1980-81; 162037 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Speeches (2 folders), 162074 (Box 27, Folder 23-24)
      - Strategy summaries, 1979; 162072 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee [Moffett], 162075 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Transcript: Radio-TV Reports, November 14-15, 1979; 143935 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - Transcripts: Issues & Answers, July 6, 1980; 143898 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - US Petroleum, 162073 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - White House mess list, 1979; 162076 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Reports, Briefing Book, 1979-1980; 176179
      - Department of Energy. Annual Report to Congress, v. 1, 1979; 176180 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - Department of Energy. Conservation Objectives, Calendar year, 1980; 176181 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Department of Energy. Draft Policy, Programming and Fiscal Guidance, FY 1982-1986; 176182 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - Department of Energy. Reducing U.S. Oil Vulnerability, November 10, 1980; 176183 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Secretary of Energy Overview Briefing Book, n.d.; 176184 (Box 27, Folder 35-36)
- Series IV. Oversize Materials, 161953
  - Secretary of Energy scrapbooks, 1979-1981; 143994 (Box 28)
  - Coca-Cola Commercials, 165678 (Box 29)
  - Architectural drawings: Herring Hall - Ground floor, building sections, elevations, 1982; 161954 (Drawer 148, Item 9)
- Series V. Addendum, 176185
  - Sub-Series I. Deputy Secretary of Defense and Secretary of Energy: Testimonials, Speeches, Remarks, Talking Points, 1977-1981; 176186
    - 12 Mar - 2 May 1977, 176188 (Box 29a, Folder 1)
    - 17 May - 7 June 1977, 176189 (Box 29a, Folder 2)
    - 23 June - 1 September 1977, 176190 (Box 29a, Folder 3)
    - 16 September - 30 November 1977, 176191 (Box 29a, Folder 4)
    - 10 January - 9 February 1978, 176192 (Box 29a, Folder 5)
    - 27 February - 25 May 1978, 176193 (Box 29a, Folder 6)
    - 15 June - 4 October 1978, 176194 (Box 29a, Folder 7)
    - 10 November - 30 December 1978, 176195 (Box 29a, Folder 8)
    - 30 January - 15 February 1979, 176196 (Box 29a, Folder 9)
    - 21 February - 30 July 1979, 176197 (Box 29a, Folder 10)
    - 24 July - 24 September 1979, 176198 (Box 29a, Folder 11)
    - 26 September - 26 October 1979, 176199 (Box 29a, Folder 12)
    - 1 November - 31 December 1979, 176200 (Box 29a, Folder 13)
    - 8 January - 31 January 1980, 176201 (Box 29a, Folder 14)
    - 4 February - 27 February 1980, 176202 (Box 29a, Folder 15)
    - 28 February - 27 March 1980, 176203 (Box 29a, Folder 16)
    - 2 April - 6 May 1980, 176204 (Box 29a, Folder 17)
    - 15 May - 12 June 1980, 176205 (Box 29a, Folder 18)
    - 17 June - 15 July 1980, 176206 (Box 29a, Folder 19)
    - 3 September - 9 October 1980, 176207 (Box 29a, Folder 20)
    - 16 October 1980 - January 1981, 176208 (Box 29a, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series II. Memoir, 176187
    - Interview with Charles W. Duncan Jr. March 6, 1996, 177861 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Research Charles W. Duncan, Jr., 177862 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Charles W. Duncan, Jr. Personal Data, 177863 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Family of Charles W. Duncan and Mary Lillian House, 177864 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Annotated Questions and Handwritten notes, 177865 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - SP Issue, February 7, 2012`, 177867 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - SP Issue: Rupp Presidential Search, February 10, 2012, 177866 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Duncan House Company, July 28, 2011, 177868 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Draft: Duncan Coffee October 6, 2011, 177869 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Misc. A-J Notes, 177870 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Draft of Chapter 1: Beginnings, Chapter 2: Duncan Coffee, Notes and interview questions, 177871 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Multiple Drafts of Chapter 1: Beginnings, 177872 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Draft of Chapters 2-12, 177873 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Draft of Chapter 2: Duncan Coffee with some annotation, 177874 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 1: Beginnings; Chapter 2: Duncan Coffee, 177875 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 2 with title change, 177876 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 1: From Tobacco to Coffee, 177877 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapters 1-5, 177878 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapter 1: Tobacco to Coffee; Chapter 2: Early Years, 177879 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Interview Transcript - Military, October 7, 2011, 177880 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Interview Transcript Chapters 2-4, Duncan House, October 13, 2011, 177881 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Draft Chapters 2-4, 177882 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Handwritten Draft: Top of 13, 177883 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 2-4, 177884 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Partial Draft of Chapter 5: Coca Cola Atlanta, 177885 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 3: Duncan Coffee; Chapter 4: Coca Cola Europe, 177886 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Draft of Chapter 1: From Tobacco to Coffee; Chapter 2: Early Years, 177887 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Handwritten Draft Coca-Cola, 177888 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 1-7, 177889 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 1-6, 177890 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 9: Education, 177891 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 6: Washington, Defense Dept., 177892 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 9: Education, 177893 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Draft of Chapter 11: Public Companies, 177894 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 10: Charity, 177895 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Draft of Chapters 11-13, 177896 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Draft of Chapter 12: Public Companies, 177897 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 7-9, 177898 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 1-5, 177899 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Annotated Draft of Chapter 7: Washington, Energy Department, 177900 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 3-7, 177901 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Draft of Chapter 7: Washington, Energy Dept.; Chapter 8: Houston After Washington, 177902 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Draft Chapter 4: Coca-Cola Europe, 177903 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Draft Chapter 12: Public Companies, 177904 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 9: Education K-12, 177905 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Annaotated Draft Chapter 9: Education K-12, 177906 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Annotated Draft and Notes Chapter 12: Public Companies, 177907 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 1-6, 177908 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 7-14, 177909 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Draft Chapter 2: Early Years, 177911 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapters 9-14, 177912 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 2-9, 177913 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 11-12, 177914 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10, 177915 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177916 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177917 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177918 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177919 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177920 (Box 30, Folder 59)